Guide to the Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South Records, 1940-1997 and undated, bulk 1993-1997 RL.00170
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Printed Materials Series (PM), ca. 1940-1997 (bulk 1993-1997) [RESTRICTED], 9 boxes
  - Orangeburg, S.C. and Environs (Box PM7)
    - Roland, Harold (Box PM7)
    - Sharrow, Marion (Box PM7)
    - Smith, Haulean (Box PM7)
    - Sulton, James, Jr. (Box PM7)
    - Thompson, Nettie (Box PM7)
    - Townsend, Zack (Box PM7)
    - Twiggs, Leo (Box PM7)
    - Walker, Cloria (Box PM7)
    - Washington, Camilla (Box PM7)
    - Williams, Ethel (Box PM7)
    - Wright, Minnie (Box PM7)
    - Zimmerman, Geraldyne (Box PM7)
  - St. Helena, S.C. and Environs
    - Atkins, Earnestine (Box PM7)
    - Barnwell, Rosalie (Box PM7)
    - Beasley, Jonathon (Box PM7)
    - Brown, George (Box PM7)
    - Browne, Corinne (Box PM7)
    - Bryan, Helen (Box PM7)
    - Bryant, Eddie (Box PM7)
    - Bundick, Elizabeth (Box PM7)
    - Carr, Peter (Box PM7)
    - Chaplin, Eva (Box PM7)
    - Daise, Kathleen (Box PM7)
    - Frazier, Coazell (Box PM7)
    - Gaston, Irene (Box PM7)
    - Holmes, Ercell (Box PM7)
    - Holmes, Laura (Box PM7)
    - Holmes, Lula (Box PM7)
    - Holmes, William (Box PM7)
    - Jones, Emma (Box PM7)
    - Legree, Joseph (Box PM7)
    - Major, Evangeline (Box PM7)
    - Mann, Etta (Box PM7)
    - Middleton, Richard (Box PM7)
    - Nesbit, Louise (Box PM7)
    - Patterson, Alexandria (Box PM7)
    - Singleton, D. (Box PM7)
    - Singleton, Kato (Box PM7)
    - Small, Henry (Box PM7)
    - Weathers, George (Box PM7)
    - Willborn, Isaac (Box PM7)
    - Williams, Jonathan (Box PM7)
    - Wright, Robbie (Box PM7)
  - Summerton, S.C. and Environs
    - Allen, Ida (Box PM7)
    - Allen, Johnny (Box PM7)
    - Anderson, Willie Mae (Box PM7)
    - Bethune, Thelmer (Box PM7)
    - Briggs, Eliza (Box PM7)
    - Briggs, Willie Mae (Box PM7)
    - Butler, B. (Box PM7)
    - Canty, John (Box PM7)
    - Canty, Mary (Box PM7)
    - Carter, Mamie (Box PM7)
    - Chandler, Janette (Box PM7)
    - DeLaine, Marguirite (Box PM7)
    - Doctor-Wearing, Alice (Box PM7)
    - Dow, Willine (Box PM7)
    - Fleming, Abraham (Box PM7)
    - Flood, John (Box PM7)
    - Frierson, Carnetta (Box PM7)
    - Frierson, Mary (Box PM7)
    - Georgia, Robert (Box PM7)
    - Gordon, Sammy, Jr. (Box PM7)
    - Gray, Ruben (Box PM7)
    - Green, Melison (Box PM7)
    - Gregory, Celestine (Box PM7)
    - Howard, Sallie (Box PM7)
    - Kennedy, Chars (Box PM7)
    - Leneau, Octavia (Box PM7)
    - Levy, Moses (Box PM7)
    - McCray, Josephine (Box PM7)
    - Nelson, Margaret (Box PM7)
    - Parks, Leola (Box PM7)
    - Poole, Lorene (Box PM7)
    - Ragin, General (Box PM7)
    - Richardson, Ruth (Box PM7)
    - Richburg, Joseph (Box PM7)
    - Smith, Abraham (Box PM7)
    - Smith, Elease (Box PM7)
    - Smith, Haulean (Box PM7)
    - Walters, Katie (Box PM7)
    - Washington, Sallie (Box PM7)
    - Williams, Cornelias (Box PM7)
    - Young, Samuel (Box PM7)
  - Tallahassee, Fla. and Environs
    - Anderson, Dora (Box PM7)
    - andrews, Malachia (Box PM7)
    - Boardly, Barbara (Box PM7)
    - Campbell, Witt (Box PM7)
    - Carr, Carrie (Box PM7)
    - Clausell, Bernyce (Box PM7)
    - Davis, Peggy (Box PM7)
    - Diallo, Mary (Box PM7)
    - Dixie, A. (Box PM7)
    - Dixie, Laura (Box PM7)
    - Dixie, Samuel (Box PM7)
    - Eaton, James (Box PM7)
    - Farmer, Martha (Box PM7)
    - Gaines, Mary (Box PM7)
    - Griffin, Robert (Box PM7)
    - Hackley, Sallie (Box PM7)
    - Harris, Bessie (Box PM7)
    - Hogans, Angelina (Box PM7)
    - Howell, Aquilina (Box PM7)
    - Huntley, John (Box PM7)
    - Jefferson, Harrieta (Box PM7)
    - Jones, Dorothy (Box PM7)
    - Kelly, Vivian (Box PM7)
    - Kemp, Ethel (Box PM7)
    - King, Gertrude (Box PM7)
    - Lewis, Clarence (Box PM8)
    - Matheus, Ellen (Box PM8)
    - McClendon, Mavis (Box PM8)
    - Miller, Gertrude (Box PM8)
    - Mungen, Robert (Box PM8)
    - Nims, H. (Box PM8)
    - Palmer, James (Box PM8)
    - Parker, Florida (Box PM8)
    - Peacock, Alice (Box PM8)
    - Perry, Benjamin (Box PM8)
    - Robinson, Lillie (Box PM8)
    - Russell, Sue (Box PM8)
    - Sanford, Lessie (Box PM8)
    - Simmons, Sarah (Box PM8)
    - Smith, Charles (Box PM8)
    - Speed, Cornelius (Box PM8)
    - Thorpe, Annette (Box PM8)
    - Thorpe, Edwin (Box PM8)
    - Walker, Courtney (Box PM8)
    - Washington, Samuel, Jr. (Box PM8)
    - Williams, Gertrude (Box PM8)
    - Williams, Myrtle (Box PM8)
    - Wilson, Roosevelt (Box PM8)
    - Young, Daisey (Box PM8)
  - Tuskegee, Ala. and Environs
    - Baldwin, Wilhelmina (Box PM8)
    - Beasley, David (Box PM8)
    - Bentley, Frank (Box PM8)
    - Brown, Cordelia (Box PM8)
    - Donald, Edward (Box PM8)
    - Ferrell, George (Box PM8)
    - Ford, Johnny (Box PM8)
    - Graham, Mai (Box PM8)
    - Grant, Ernest (Box PM8)
    - Green, Elbert (Box PM8)
    - Hall, Annie (Box PM8)
    - Hall, Ezell (Box PM8)
    - Hooten, Henry (Box PM8)
    - Hooten, Lillian (Box PM8)
    - Jones, Ira (Box PM8)
    - Jones, Wilhelmina (Box PM8)
    - Judkins, Marian (Box PM8)
    - Judkins, Robert (Box PM8)
    - Lee, Detroit (Box PM8)
    - Lyles, Demetrice (Box PM8)
    - Mayberry, Bennie (Box PM8)
    - McCorvey, Sandy (Box PM8)
    - Paris, George (Box PM8)
    - Pinkard, Otis (Box PM8)
    - Pointer, Ann (Box PM8)
    - Pollard, Charles (Box PM8)
    - Poole, Georgia (Box PM8)
    - Price, John (Box PM8)
    - Quinn, Bettie (Box PM8)
    - Quinn, Hersey (Box PM8)
    - Randolph, L. (Box PM8)
    - Robinson, Amelia (Box PM8)
    - Sullins, Della (Box PM8)
    - Taylor, William (Box PM8)
    - Thomas, Elaine (Box PM8)
    - Walker, Archie (Box PM8)
    - Walker, Claudius (Box PM8)
    - Walker, Ferdie (Box PM8)
    - Wells, Ida (Box PM8)
    - Whitehead, Willie (Box PM8)
    - Woodson, James (Box PM8)
    - Wright, Jessie (Box PM8)
    - Young, Kenneth (Box PM8)
  - Wilmington, N.C. and Environs
    - Alexander, Camille (Box PM8)
    - Baker, George (Box PM8)
    - Berry, Lisbon (Box PM8)
    - Berry, Shirley (Box PM8)
    - Boykin, Hartford (Box PM8)
    - Bryant, Charles (Box PM8)
    - Burnett, Elijah (Box PM8)
    - Chestnut, Carter (Box PM8)
    - Childs, William (Box PM8)
    - Coco, Joan (Box PM8)
    - Cooper, Ida (Box PM8)
    - Davis, George (Box PM8)
    - Davis, Ruth (Box PM8)
    - Donaldson, Henry (Box PM8)
    - Donaldson, Laura (Box PM8)
    - Epps, Doris (Box PM8)
    - Forden, Harry (Box PM8)
    - Fredlaw, Clarence (Box PM8)
    - Fredlaw, Margaret (Box PM8)
    - Gerald, Ethel (Box PM8)
    - Harris, Edna (Box PM8)
    - Harris, Elvenia (Box PM8)
    - Harris, Jeanne (Box PM8)
    - Hassell, Lula (Box PM8)
    - Haynes, Edward (Box PM8)
    - Henry, Charlie (Box PM8)
    - Johnson, Ezell (Box PM8)
    - Jones, Alexander (Box PM8)
    - Kirby, Dorothy (Box PM8)
    - Logan, Eugene (Box PM8)
    - Logan, Willie (Box PM8)
    - MacRae, George (Box PM8)
    - Mallette, John (Box PM8)
    - Mallette, Renée (Box PM8)
    - McCrae, Aaron (Box PM8)
    - McCrimmon, Marvis (Box PM8)
    - Morris, Willie (Box PM8)
    - Neal, Margaret (Box PM8)
    - Nixon, Cornelius (Box PM8)
    - O'Dell, Beryl (Box PM8)
    - Rogers, Margaret (Box PM8)
    - Saulter, Elizabeth (Box PM8)
    - Session, Audrey (Box PM8)
    - Smith, Lillian (Box PM8)
    - Smith, Rebecca (Box PM8)
    - Spaulding, John (Box PM8)
    - Spencer, Leonard (Box PM8)
    - Swain, Ernest (Box PM8)
    - Tate, Katherine (Box PM8)
    - Thomas, Esther (Box PM8)
    - Thomas, Roderick (Box PM8)
    - Todd, Bertha (Box PM8)
    - Todd, Edward (Box PM8)
    - Upperman, Leroy (Box PM8)
    - Wade, Alene (Box PM8)
    - Wade, David (Box PM8)
    - Wade, Mamie (Box PM8)
    - White, Margaret (Box PM8)
    - Williams, Lucille (Box PM8)
    - Wilson, Lloyd (Box PM8)
    - Woods, Dorothy (Box PM8)
  - ACCESS RESTRICTED PRINTED MATERIALS (Box PM9)
    - Albany, Ga. and Environs
      - Bryant, Ella (Box PM9)
      - Flowers, Aurie (Box PM9)
      - George, Stine (Box PM9)
      - Grant, James (Box PM9)
      - King, Carol (Box PM9)
      - Lilly, Dan (Box PM9)
      - Sherrod, Charles (Box PM9)
    - Arkansas
      - Denton, Zelma (Box PM9)
      - Gunthrope, Myrtle (Box PM9)
    - Birmingham, Ala. and Environs
      - Henderson, Larry (Box PM9)
    - Charlotte, N.C. and Environs
      - Cornelius, Doreatha (Box PM9)
      - Givens, Helen (Box PM9)
      - Hawkins, Reginald (Box PM9)
      - Pickens, Magnolia (Box PM9)
    - Durham, N.C. and Environs
      - Price, Hastie (Box PM9)
      - Turner, Margaret (Box PM9)
    - LeFlore Co., Miss. and Environs
      - Hammond, Jimmie (Box PM9)
      - Howard, Frank (Box PM9)
      - King, Mrs. (Box PM9)
      - Kinnard, Arthur (Box PM9)
    - Memphis, Tenn. and Environs
      - Lewis Center. Women's Club (Box PM9)
    - Mid-Michigan
      - Byrd, Sanford (Box PM9)
    - New Bern, N.C. and Environs
      - Bell, Emma (Box PM9)
    - New Iberia, La. and Environs
      - Journet, Inez (Box PM9)
    - Orangeburg, S.C. and Environs
      - Mathews, Sarah (Box PM9)
      - Reagan, Mrs. (Box PM9)
      - Smith, Mr. (Box PM9)
      - Weise, Aunt (Box PM9)
    - St. Helena, S.C. and Environs
      - Brown, Leroy (Box PM9)
      - Carr, Rebecca (Box PM9)
      - Henderson, David (Box PM9)
      - Orr, Isaiah (Box PM9)
    - Summerton, S.C. and Environs
      - Pearson, Ferdinand (Box PM9)
      - Wells, Julia (Box PM9)
      - Wright, Minnie (Box PM9)
    - Tallahassee, Fla. and Environs
      - Pinochle Club (Box PM9)
      - Stephens, Edwina (Box PM9)
    - Tuskegee, Ala. and Environs
      - Cooley, Fannie (Box PM9)
      - Ducksworth, Lee (Box PM9)
      - Marable, Clarence (Box PM9)
      - Owens, Johnnie (Box PM9)
      - Toland, Frank (Box PM9)
    - Wilmington, N.C. and Environs
      - Wallace, Alfreda (Box PM9)
      - Williston Sr. High (Box PM9)
- Transcripts Series (TR), 1993-1997, 18 boxes
  The Transcripts Series, 1993-1997, includes transcripts of 314 interviews in the Behind the Veil collection. Interviews were chosen for transcription on the basis of the quality and content of particular interviews, and toward the goal of providing transcripts that cover the geographical and topical range of the collection. They are arranged alphabetically by site and by surname within. The transcripts also exist as electronic documents. A disk directories log exists. Contact Research Services staff for assistance.
  - Albany, Ga. and Environs
    - Bradford, Martha (Box TR1)
    - Chatmon, Thomas (Box TR1)
    - Cuffie, Roosevelt (Box TR1)
    - Flowers, AurieBell (Box TR1)
    - Gamble, Edward (Box TR1)
    - George, Doris (Box TR1)
    - George, Stein (Box TR1)
    - Hall, James (Box TR1)
    - Hudson, Irene (Box TR1)
    - Nelson, Mamie (Box TR1)
    - Pitts, Anna (Box TR1)
    - Searles, Arthur (Box TR1)
    - Sherrod, Shirley (Box TR1)
    - Stewart, Ada (Box TR1)
    - Watkins, Jurl (Box TR1)
    - Wells, Samuel (Box TR1)
    - Williams, Curtis (Box TR1)
    - Williams, Leola (Box TR2)
  - Arkansas
    - Caldwell, Ernest (Box TR2)
    - Chism, Tolbert (Box TR2)
    - Davidson, Geraldine (Box TR2)
    - Dennis, Dora (Box TR2)
    - Howard, Helen (Box TR2)
    - Jones, Julice and Le Ester (Box TR2)
    - Kirby, Money, and Anne Kirby (Box TR2)
    - Lowe, Mattie Bell (Box TR2)
    - Lucas, Willie (Box TR2)
    - Malone, William (Box TR2)
    - Mitchell, Cleaster (Box TR2)
    - Nash, Thelma (Box TR2)
    - Swanigan, Katie (Box TR2)
    - Tims, W.C. (Box TR2)
    - Tunage, Elizabeth (Box TR2)
    - Vaughn, Thomas (Box TR2)
    - White, Samella (Box TR2)
    - Williams, Oliver (Box TR2)
    - Woods, Delores, and Thelma Woods Nash (Box TR2)
  - Baltimore, MD and Environs
    - Holloway, George (Box TR3)
      [Also listed under Memphis, Tenn. and Environs where the majority of interview seems to speak of]
  - Birmingham, Ala. and Environs
    - Alexander, Leon (Box TR3)
    - Archie, Johnnie (Box TR3)
    - Brown, Earl (Box TR3)
    - Brown, George L. (Box TR3)
    - Clarke, Juanita (Box TR3)
    - Davis, Blanche (Box TR3)
    - Fisher, John (Box TR3)
    - Gratton, Charles (Box TR3)
    - Hendricks, Lola (Box TR3)
    - Monroe, Irene (Box TR3)
    - Patton, William (Box TR3)
    - Sanders, Gertrude (Box TR3)
    - Taylor, Lovell (Box TR3)
    - Williams, Mazie (Box TR3)
    - Williams, Roosevelt (Box TR3)
    - Wilson, Alberta (Box TR3)
  - Charlotte, N.C. and Environs
    - Adams, Wilhelmenia (Box TR3)
    - Alexander, Zechariah (Box TR3)
    - Cavers, Walter (Box TR3)
    - Davis, Price (Box TR4)
    - Ely, Vermelle (Box TR4)
    - Hawkins, Reginald (Box TR4)
    - Holmes, Walter (Box TR4)
    - Jones, J.Charles (Box TR4)
    - Lynch, Lucille (Box TR4)
    - Morris, Ruth (Box TR4)
    - Mungo, Alma (Box TR4)
    - Neal, Margaret (Box TR4)
    - Rann, EmeryDr. (Box TR4)
    - Robinson, Violet (Box TR4)
    - Steele, Dorothy (Box TR4)
    - Taylor, Rosita (Box TR4)
    - Thompson, Jean (Box TR4)
    - Wilson, Catherine (Box TR4)
  - Durham, N.C. and Environs
    - Blue, Ila (Box TR4)
    - Brodie, Arthur (Box TR5)
    - Bryant, Artelia (Box TR5)
    - Butterfield, G.K. (Box TR5)
    - Crockett, Manuel (Box TR5)
    - Faulk, Marie (Box TR5)
    - Fitts, Howard (Box TR5)
    - Garrett, York (Box TR5)
    - Harris, Mable (Box TR5)
    - Lucas, Julia (Box TR5)
    - Lyons, Theresa (Box TR5)
    - Mimms, Horace (Box TR5)
    - Page, Mildred (Box TR5)
    - Quigless, Milton (Box TR5)
    - Rivera, Alexander (Box TR5)
    - Scarborough, George, Jr. (Box TR5)
    - Taylor, Jennie (Box TR5)
    - Thorpe, Amelia Pride (Box TR5)
    - Turner, Margaret (Box TR5)
    - White, Nathaniel, Sr. (Box TR5)
  - Enfield, N.C. and Environs
    - Boddie, Mary (Box TR6)
    - Bullock, Lester (Box TR6)
    - Farmer, Bertha and Anthony (Box TR6)
    - Fenner, Lillie (Box TR6)
    - Forney, Myrtle (Box TR6)
    - Grant, Florenza (Box TR6)
    - Grant, Matthew (Box TR6)
    - Hinton, Katherine (Box TR6)
    - Johnson, Jack William (Box TR6)
    - Johnson, Ruth (Box TR6)
    - McWilliams, Ada (Box TR6)
    - Plummer, Vera (Box TR6)
    - Scott, Jasper, Louise Scott, and Eddy Francis (Box TR6)
    - Smith, Lillie, Bernice Bronson, and Pam Reynolds (Two Parts) (Box TR6)
    - Thorne, Annie (Box TR7)
    - Tillery, Roy (Box TR7)
    - Weathersbee, Sue (Box TR7)
    - Wills, Almyra (Box TR7)
    - Wills, Hubert, and Almyra Wills (Box TR7)
  - LeFlore Co., Miss. and Environs
    - Alexander, Essie (Box TR7)
    - Bays, Georgia (Box TR7)
    - Bowie, Eura (Box TR7)
    - Clayborn, Arthur (Box TR7)
    - Davis, Arnette (Box TR7)
    - Davis, William (Box TR7)
    - Federick, Booker T. (Box TR7)
    - Flemming, Cora (Box TR7)
    - Gibson, O.C. (Box TR7)
    - Giles, Alice (Box TR7)
    - Jackson, Ruthie (Box TR8)
    - Johnson, Mandie (Box TR8)
    - Livingston, Daisy (Box TR8)
    - Lucas, Maurice (Box TR8)
    - Matthews, David (Box TR8)
    - Pitts, Elizabeth (Box TR8)
    - Reed, Willie (Box TR8)
    - Rolling, Susie (Box TR8)
    - Rose, Richard (Box TR8)
    - Taylor, Julia (Box TR8)
    - White, Bernice (Box TR8)
    - Williams, H.J. (Box TR8)
    - Young, Chris, Sr. (Box TR8)
  - Memphis, Tenn. and Environs
    - Boyd, Leroy (Box TR8)
      [Interviews from 1983 and 1995 are included]
    - Branch, Lanetha (Box TR8)
    - Butler, Willie (Box TR8)
    - Cooper, Barbara (Box TR8)
    - Cooper, John, Barbara Cooper, and Edgar Hunt (Box TR8)
    - Cross, Blondale (Box TR9)
    - Forest, Earl (Box TR9)
    - Fort, Marie (Box TR9)
    - Griffin, Lovie Mae (Box TR9)
    - Harrell, Willie (Box TR9)
    - Holloway, George (Box TR9)
      [Transcript is filed under Baltimore, MD which appears on the front of the transcript]
    - Hunt, Edgar (Box TR9)
    - Jones, Amy (Box TR9)
    - Lewis, Charles (Box TR9)
    - Malden, RosaLea (Box TR9)
    - Pearson, Frank (Box TR9)
    - Robinson, Mary (Box TR9)
    - Sims, Constant, and Earl Forest (Box TR9)
    - Spencer, Robert (Box TR9)
    - Strong Jones, Otha B. (Box TR9)
    - Thompson, Ralph (Box TR9)
    - Veazy, Rodie (Box TR9)
    - Ware, Elizabeth (Box TR9)
    - Wilson, Emogene (Box TR9)
  - Muhlenberg Co., Ky. and Environs
    - Dulin, Mary (Box TR9)
    - Eaves, Elicie (Box TR10)
    - Gilmore, Sydney Jr. (Box TR10)
    - Goins, Mallie (Box TR10)
  - New Bern, N.C. and Environs
    - Attmore, Arlestus (Box TR10)
    - Best, Haywood and Stephen (Box TR10)
    - Campbell, Sarah (Box TR10)
    - Carter, Dorcas (Box TR10)
    - Clemmons, Ernestine (Box TR10)
    - Gavin, Annie (Box TR10)
    - Lewis, James, and Marion Lewis (Box TR10)
    - Roberts, Mary (Box TR10)
    - Sutton, Georgia (Box TR10)
    - Wade, Harriet (Box TR10)
  - New Iberia, La. and Environs
    - Auguster, Edran (Box TR10)
    - Bernard, Lucille (Box TR10)
    - Bijou, Hattie (Box TR11)
    - Bijou, Prosper (Box TR11)
    - Blaise, Edward (Box TR11)
    - Chassion, Jessie (Box TR11)
    - Harding, William (Box TR11)
    - Hills, Erline (Box TR11)
    - James, Herman, Sr. (Box TR11)
    - Knatt, Clement and Willie Mae (Box TR11)
    - Manuel, Armstrong (Box TR11)
    - Mitchell, Maizel (Box TR11)
    - Polk, Edith (Box TR11)
    - Polk, Matthew (Box TR11)
    - Russell, James, folder 1 of 2 (Box TR11)
    - Russell, James, folder 2 of 2 (Box TR12)
    - Russell, Nancy (Box TR12)
    - Smith, Alfred James (Box TR12)
    - Sutton, Virginia (Box TR12)
    - Thompson, William (Box TR12)
    - Volter, John (Box TR12)
    - Zepherin, William (Box TR12)
  - New Orleans, La. and Environs
    - Aaron, Dolores (Box TR12)
    - Borders, Florence (Box TR12)
    - Boucree, John (Box TR12)
    - Bouise, Louise (Box TR12)
    - Caitone, Beverly (Box TR12)
    - Cappie, Herbert (Box TR12)
    - Cappie, Irene (Box TR13)
    - Cheri, Emmett (Box TR13)
    - Dave, Peter (Box TR13)
    - Davillier, Brenda Bozant (Box TR13)
  - Norfolk, Va. and Environs
    - Branchcomb, Flossie (Box TR13)
    - Brickers, Alease (Box TR13)
    - Brown, John W. (Box TR13)
    - Cherry, Olivia (Box TR13)
    - Coker, William (Box TR13)
    - Edmonds, Marian (Box TR13)
    - Hayslette, Elnora (Box TR13)
    - Johnson, Harvey, Jr. (Box TR13)
    - Johnson, Jessie (Box TR13)
    - Linyer, William (Box TR13)
    - Mitchell, Alma (Box TR13)
    - Porter, Clestine (Box TR13)
    - Studivant, Lenora (Box TR13)
    - Williams, Hortense (Box TR13)
    - Wyatt, George (Box TR13)
  - Orangeburg, S.C. and Environs
    - Adams, Benjamin (Box TR14)
    - Brunson, John (Box TR14)
    - Henderson, Ernest (Box TR14)
    - Jamison, Annie (Box TR14)
    - Jamison, Marion (Box TR14)
    - Jenkins, Barbara (Box TR14)
    - Montgomery, Eugene (Box TR14)
    - Roland, Harold (Box TR14)
    - Thompson, Nettie (Box TR14)
  - St. Helena, S.C. and Environs
    - Brown, George, and Joseph Prince Legree (Box TR14)
    - Browne, Corrine (Box TR14)
    - Bryant, Eddie (Box TR14)
    - Carr, Peter (Box TR14)
    - Daise, Kathleen (Box TR14)
    - Legree, Joseph (Box TR14)
    - Middleton, Richard (Box TR14)
    - Nesbit, Louise (Box TR15)
    - Small, Henry (Box TR15)
    - Wilborn, Isaac (Box TR15)
    - Williams, Jonathan (Box TR15)
    - Wright, Robbie (Box TR15)
  - Summerton, S.C. and Environs
    - Allen, Johhny and Ida Bell Allen (Box TR15)
    - Bethune, Thelmer (Box TR15)
    - Butler, B.O. (Box TR15)
    - Canty, John (Box TR15)
    - Canty, Mary (Box TR15)
    - Delaine, Marguirite (Box TR15)
    - Georgia, Robert (Box TR15)
    - Howard, Sallie (Box TR15)
    - Levy, Moses (Box TR15)
    - McCray, Josephine (Box TR15)
    - Nelson, Margaret (Box TR15)
    - Pearson, Ferdinand (Box TR15)
    - Poole, Lorene (Box TR15)
    - Richburg, Joseph (Box TR15)
    - Smith, Abraham (Box TR15)
    - Wells, Julia (Box TR15)
    - Young, Samuel (Box TR15)
  - Tallahassee, Fla. and Environs
    - Anderson, Dora (Box TR16)
    - andrews, Malachia (Box TR16)
    - Davis, Peggy (Box TR16)
    - Dixie, A.I. (Box TR16)
    - Dixie, Laura M. and Samuel (Box TR16)
    - Dixie, Laura May (Box TR16)
    - Dixie, Samuel Lee (Box TR16)
    - Griffin, Robert (Box TR16)
    - Jefferson, Harrieta (Box TR16)
    - Parker, Florida (Box TR16)
    - Russell, Sue (Box TR16)
    - Simmons, Sarah (Box TR16)
    - Speed, Cornelius (Box TR16)
    - Walker, Courtney (Box TR16)
    - Young, Daisy (Box TR16)
  - Tuskegee, Ala. and Environs
    - Baldwin, Wihelmina (Box TR16)
    - Grant, Ernest (Box TR16)
    - Hooten, Mr. and Mrs. Henry (Box TR16)
    - Hooten, Mr. and Mrs. Henry, Duplicate copy (Box TR17)
    - Jones, Ira (Box TR17)
    - Jones, Wilhelmina (Box TR17)
    - Marable, Clarence (Box TR17)
    - Pointer, Ann (Box TR17)
    - Pointer, A. Elizabeth (Box TR17)
    - Walker, Ferdie (Box TR17)
    - Young, Kenneth (Box TR17)
    - Young, Mai (Box TR17)
  - Wilmington, N.C. and Environs
    - Childs, William (Box TR17)
    - Davis, Ruth (Box TR17)
    - Donaldson, Henry (Box TR17)
    - Donaldson, Laura (Box TR17)
    - McCrae, Rev. Aaron, Sr. (Box TR17)
    - Rogers, Margaret (Box TR17)
    - Smith, Lillian (Box TR18)
    - Swain, Ernest (Box TR18)
    - Todd, Bertha (Box TR18)
- Accession 2000-0183
  - box 1 (Box 1)
  - Master Tape Series
    - Durham, N.C. and Environs
      - Braswell, Martha; Interview #1; Janet Reilly, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Braswell, Martha; Interview #2; Janet Reilly, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Goodwin, Margaret S.; Intv. #1; Kristin Lee, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Goodwin, Margaret S.; Intv. #2; Kristin Lee, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Johnson, Georgie; Interview #1; Interviewer Keisha Roberts, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Jones, Dorothy; Intv. #1; Kristin Koeker, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Jones, Dorothy; Interview #2; Kristin Koeker, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Jones, Elaine; Interview #1; Amy Murnick, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Jones, Elaine; Interview #2; Amy Murnick, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Lyons, Bettie; Interview #1; Mi Young Ryee, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Mabry, Corine; Interview #1; Interviewer: Abrielle Beaton, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Mabry, Corine; Interview #2; Interviewer: Abrielle Beaton, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Osborne, Ruby; Interview #1; Interviewer: Andrea Smith, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Osborne, Ruby; Interview #2; Andrea Smith, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Parker, Creola; Interview #1; Interviewer: Serena Rhodie, 1997 October 20, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Sarah Forgione Interview with Annie Patterson, [1 tape, Interview#1?] (Box 1)
      - Patterson, Annie; Sara Forgione; Interview #2, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Roundtree, Gwen; Interview #1; Mi Young Ryee, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Shaw, Catherine; Interview #1; Carmen Alexander, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Shaw, Catherine; Interview #2; Carmen Alexander, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Shaw, Hollis; Interview #1; Interviewer: Peter Messick, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Shaw, Hollis; 1997 November 14; Intv. #2; Peter Messick, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Theodore Speight; Intv. #1; Intv. by Will Wiseman, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Barnes, Lenzie; 1996 October 23, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Barnes, Lenzie; 1996 November 25, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Boyd, Ruth, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Bryant, Kelly; 1996 October, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Bryant, Kelly; 1996 November 15, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - Cousin, Philip R., 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Davis, Julius, 3 tapes (Box 1)
      - Smith, Mary, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Thorpe, Amelia; Intv. #1, 2 tapes (Box 1)
      - Thorpe, Amelia;Intv. #2, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - White, Nathaniel; 1996 November 11, 1 tape (Box 1)
      - White, Nathaniel; 1996 October? 14, 2 tapes (Box 1)
  - box 2 (Box 2)
  - Course Information Series, 5 folders (Box 2)
    Course syllabus, some student self-evaluations, contracts, indices, and transcript excerpts.
  - Use Tape Series, Copy 1
    - Durham, N.C. and Environs
      - box 2.1 (Box 2.1)
      - Braswell, Martha; Interview #1; Janet Reilly, 2 tapes (Box 2.1)
      - Braswell, Martha; Interview #2; Janet Reilly, 1 tape (Box 2.1)